We were playing a game of nyan-nyan with two people,
It was very interesting,
I would like to play it again.
It was too much the first time,
I couldn't answer at all,
I will do my best next time.
We both have things to reflect on,
This time, I would like to make the most of those points,
I would like to aim for 20 Nyanko this time.
See you soon!   I'll do it the other way around.......
I'll reverse it. From earlier.
Shall we do that?
Then, I'll say the nyan words.
Please do.
I'll do my best.
Next time,
Next time, I will do my best.
I'll keep the same two and a half minutes, two and a half minutes for a total of five minutes.
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready. I'm ready.
Okay, let the meow meow games begin!
All right, all right, all right. I'll do my best.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Name the convenience store.
Meow meow meow.
7-Eleven!
Okay, okay, okay.
It's a good slide.
Let's see, it starts with "moo". Nyan-nyan.
Momo. Correct.
Oh. Maybe you're making use of your reflection.
Then, let's go. Let's see... creatures in the zoo.
Well, it's a zoo, so, uh, nyanya.
Elephant. Nyanya. Deer.
No, no.
Stone. Horse.
Oh, but something, it's okay because I'll push it, but no thanks.
Snake.
No, it's not.
No, thank you, Dawn.
Dawn.
Dawn is, uh, an elephant.
Uh, more than an elephant.
Tiger.
Oh, you're right.
I'm talking nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah.
Really.
Oh, then, a few numbers just now.
Huh.
Oh, here we go.
Nyanya.
Jyuni.
Oh, that's too close.
Jyu-san.
Correct answer.
Oh. That was easy to understand.
Well, let's see, a tropical fish... For example, a tropical fish.
Nyah-nyah.
Nisshh... nisshh?
Nisshhh.
Not that way, but the way you put the words together is pretty much that way.
Nyah-nyah.
Tochippy.
Is there a theory I don't know? Is this popular? Is it famous?
Very well. Famous?
Tropical fish?
Goldfish?
But that's the line...
Love?
It's not love.
It's a tiny two.
Meow.
There is. Yes, there is.
Meow meow.
He's kind of popular. Very popular.
Popular?
Some people want to buy it.
Ah!
No?
Wuppalupalu?
No, it's not.
Huh?
Just...
Chippy?
First, first, first, first, first.
I'll ask you later.
Okay.
So...
What's for school lunch?
What? What's for school lunch?
It depends on the area.
That's right.
Meow, meow, meow.
Meow-mow-mow-mow ramen.
Ah! It's too close!
Bean-curd soup with red bean pasteStill good?
Whoa whoa whoa.
What? Red stuff?
What's red? First of all.
Red thing?
What's a red thing? A red thing...
Meow meow.
Meow meow?
Meow meow meow.
Nyaa?
That's right!
Can I say "meow"?
Meow!
What if I draw it?
What if I draw you an illustration?
Illustration?
Ribbon.
Is there a difference?
Oh, no.
It's itchy.
Okay, here we go.
Let's start the second half.
Ta-da!
Prefectures
Meow Meow Meow
Aichi
Nya Nya
Two Characters
Nyanya
Which one is it?
Is it the last one?
The one in the back?
What? What's there?
Meow!
Kumamoto Kagoshi
Two words? Shiga.
Then nya nya
Tokyo Correct!
No.1
Shonen Jump manga
Oh no, nya nya nya nya
One Piece Correct!
Bread name Nyan Nyan Nyan
Croissant Correct!
Eh, it's difficult.
Nyannyannyanny
Shibuya?
What! I grew up in Kencho!
Nyonya nyonya
I'm being told to calm down
I'm told to calm down.
I'm famous.
Very famous!
Nyanya Nyanya
I grew up in the prefectural office... so I guess we're all famous.
Prefectural office?
Which prefecture?
Not Kanto.
What?
Nya nya nya...
Nyanya!
Nagoya! Correct!
Next
Things starting with eyes
Melon
Glasses
Correct!
Great, great, great, great!
School events
School event
It's a school event
Choir Festival
Athletic festival
It's too close to call!
Nyan Nyan Nyan
Nyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyannyanny
What are your school events?
Nyan Nyan Nyan
Field day
Correct!
Perfect!
But my memory is longer than before.
I've got...
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Six?
Oh, my God!
I have...
Five.
Eleven.
I've grown!
I'm more than halfway there!
I'm ready!
Last time I did it
I was 7.
I got 11 correct!
Q2. What does a fried egg taste like?Q2. What does fried egg taste like?
Oh, there it is! It's a guppy.
Who's a guppy?
Who's a guppy? Nice to meet you, guppy.
Really? What's he look like?
He's a little guy.
Oh, the super tiny one?
Yes, a very tiny one.
The skinny little guy?
Thin little guy.
A guppy.
For a moment, I wondered if it was a betta. A betta.
Oh, it's a betta.
It seems to be a betta.
His tail is already big.
It's so big, and it's so fluffy.
So, even if you put one fish in one tank and one fish in the other tank, they fight each other.
So it looks like a fight,
So, I had to hide them with white hair or something.
I had used it before for a shoot,
I mean, I had appeared in a scene with them,
Did you fight?
We had a fight.
We were fighting.
They made a curtain with their white hair so that we couldn't see each other's faces.
How do you fight?
We were kind of close to each other, and we were kind of doing it one stroke at a time,
I'm learning a lot from this game.
Yes, it is.
I'm learning a lot.
Guppies?
Guppies.
Guppies and?
Betas.
Betta.
The sun.
Ahhh.
It is certainly red when I draw it.
It was the sun in me.
This makes me so smart.
I want to do this again.
I want to.
It's fun.
It was fun.
It's good.
I like that we're not too smart. We are.
I could see the shellfish a little bit, too.
I think it would be fun for smart people to do it,
I think it would be fun to do it with other people who are not so smart,
You should try it.
undefined